



Jakub Jurkiewicz

E-mail: jakubxjurkiewicz@gmail.com

Phone: 514 154 689

Date of birth: 16.09.1998

City: Olsztyn

Frontend Developer with 3 years of commercial experience. Software development is my passion. My current goal is to continue my professional development, expand my knowledge, gain skills both technical and soft.

Check out my portfolio page for more info: https://jxjurkiewicz.github.io/

WORK EXPERIENCE

03.2016 - 04.2024 (2 months)

• Frontend Developer | Wizcode | Freelance

Brief job description:

booking.powerso.pl

I developed a dynamic web platform from scratch revolutionizing electric vehicle (EV) charging accessibility. Leveraging React, Next.js, TypeScript, and Tailwind CSS, I engineered a seamless user experience interfacing with Google Maps API to display real-time charging locations, calculating routes for the trip considering charging stations near the route depending on the radius. Implementing a mobile-first approach, I ensured responsive design across devices, optimizing accessibility for EV drivers on-the-go.

06.2021 - 02.2024 (~3 years)

• Frontend Developer | Redicon - Software House | Olsztyn

Brief job description:

Creating scalable and responsive applications with mobile-first approach, implementing the front-end based on a graphic template, managing new features and components, integrating and configuring CMS. I created over 30 various landing pages and applications. Through this, I have acquired skills in HTML, CSS (including SASS, TailwindCSS, Bootstrap), JavaScript, TypeScript, jQuery, React, Next, PHP, working with a MySQL database, API integration, proficiency in using Photoshop, Figma, Adobe XD, Avocode, project management through Jira, Redmine, and GIT.

- → Creating Wordpress websites from scratch, management, support for Woocommerce, many popular plugins like ACF, Contact Form 7, plugins and extensions development, SEO optimization, managing databases, technical support to clients
- → Introducing new features in JavaScript, strong foundation in writing pure JS, using features from the newest versions of ECMAScript
- → Experience in utilizing TypeScript's advanced features such as interfaces, generics to improve code maintainability and scalability, type-safe development
- → Command over developing React.js components, Virtual DOM, and workflows, building interactive user interfaces, managing global state
- → API development and deployment, API calls, data fetches
- → Continuous testing and integration of builds and releases
- → Knowledge of using Linux, Windows, git version control, node packages, collaboration and graphic applications
- → Writing pure, scalable and simple code using good practices and methods e.g. BEM

09.2016 - 10.2016 (2 months)

• Intern | Redicon - Software House | Olsztyn

Brief job description:

Internship at a high school. Learning the basics of HTML, CSS and Javascript.

EDUCATION

09.2014 – 06.2018 (3 years 10 months)

• Zespół Szkół Ekonomicznych im. Mikołaja Kopernika w Olsztynie

Specialization: IT Specialist

LANGUAGE SKILLS

English: advanced **Polish:** native

SKILLS

 $HTML5 \cdot CSS3 \cdot SASS \cdot JavaScript \cdot RWD \cdot Linux \cdot PHP \cdot MySQL \cdot Git \cdot React.js \cdot jQuery \cdot TailwindCSS \cdot Bootstrap \cdot WordPress \cdot Node.js \cdot SEO \cdot Next.js \cdot TypeScript \cdot Zustand$

COURSES, CERTIFICATES

11.2018

• Search engines: website positioning and optimization

Host: ProcessTeam

11.2018

• Managing Google Apps for Work - G Suite

Host: ProcessTeam

10.2018

• Project management "Session" - part II.

Host: ProcessTeam

08.2018

• Qualification E.14 Web and database application development and administration

1	\cap	1.2	n	1	7
	u		u		•

• Geoinformatics systems in practice with field data acquisition and processing

Host: VCC

08.2017

• Qualification E.13 Design of local area networks and network administration

08.2016

• Qualification E.12 Assembly and operation of personal computers and peripheral devices

HOBBIES

automotive, personal development, mixed martial arts

LINKS

Github

https://github.com/jxjurkiewicz

Linkedin

https://www.linkedin.com/in/jakub-jurkiewicz-970723286/

Portfolio

https://jxjurkiewicz.github.io/